I see it being such a huge huge problem
where when guys come to me and I see how
many alcoholic drinks they're drinking
per week, I don't even have to read the
rest of the questionnaire to say you're
going to be having side effects with
your treatment. So, I've seen that
you've done videos explaining how weed
and alcohol are just completely
derailing not just bodybuilding
progress, but all health progress in
general. Can you explain to the guys in
in in in your way and in your words why
you can't smoke weed regularly and drink
alcohol regularly and be fit, healthy,
and feel
>> in, you know, in a lot of America, you
can still be considered healthy, but
you're actively taking poison.
That alcohol is [__] poison. Period.
It is the worst [__] you could do.
You're better off snorting coke and
shooting heroin than doing alcohol.
Assuming that it's sterile needle
practices and it's pure cocaine in a
reasonable amount and it's, you know,
pure heroin in a reasonable amount, not
laced with fentanyl, not like you're
used to 20% pure and then you get
slipped some pure stuff and you
overdose. I'm not talking about that
[__] I'm talking about the actual
medical physiological changes that occur
from cocaine and from heroin are way
better than the [__] that happens on
alcohol. As far as weed goes, the worst
thing about weed is that you're smoking.
That edibles or vaping in theory, if
there's not the flavoring agents, it
causes popcorn lung. In theory, that's
not as bad. But the study showed that
marijuana delays reaction times in
pilots for up to 3 weeks after they use
it once. Also, marijuana causes
something similar to SHBG to be
released, which mops up testosterone and
basically lowers your testosterone
effective androgen levels, which makes
you relative estrogen dominant. So, like
30 years ago, girls didn't like d
sleeping with dudes who smoked weed
because they thought that they had lower
sex drives. that girls avoided dudes
that smoked weed. It was consider like
he smokes weeds and plays video games
and eats pizzas and drinks Mountain Dew,
he's going to be bad in bed versus the
guy who doesn't smoke weed, doesn't
drink, lifts weights and exercises, then
he's going to be better in bed. So,
girls gravitated towards physically fit
dudes because they wanted a good lay
that I don't know what the [__] they
make their criteria based on now with
dad bods and feelings and all that [__]
But, I mean, the point is is before all
of the gender dist disruption that's
occurred in the last 10 years, girls
were pretty straightforward and normal.
And it was just like, "Oh, that dude's
hot. I want to [__] him." And then they
would. And then it's like it made it
simple. It's like get hot.
Money is okay, but get as hot as you can
and girls will want to [__] you. And
then you don't have to do anything. You
just have to smile, say, "Yeah," and
talk and answer questions or ask them
questions and [__] just worked out. Now
I have no [__] idea what the girls
are looking for. They're crazy. But back
used to be simple that get them off,
they come back for more, and that was
all there was to it. So why on earth
would you take drugs that make you worse
in bed?
Why? And it's like, well, I'm never
gonna get laid anyway because I'm ugly
and girls don't like me. It's like,
okay, but
but you're gonna be better at video
games if you're not high on weed. You
know, everything you do is better if
you're not on weed. You feel better on
weed until you're dependent on it. Now,
you need to smoke weed just to feel
normal. Now, you roll out of bed, smoke
weed, you're high for 10 minutes, and
then you have to smoke weed every 30
minutes for the whole day just to feel
normal. and you're exhausted and you
have something called a motivational
syndrome and you accomplish nothing.
Now with the alcohol thing, the alcohol
ties up your liver. It's got to use
alcohol dehydrogenase. The alcohol
dehydrogenase uses water. So it's
dehydrating you constantly and then more
importantly it creates anifreeze which
is a toxin. And then your body has to
burn the alcohol before it can burn fat.
So, alcohol completely derails any goals
in athletics or physique.
Now, you're going to be like, well,
there's people like Michael Phelps got
eight gold medals and he smoked weed,
right? And he would have gotten nine if
he didn't. You know, it's like the same
thing that like Mike Israel said. It's
like maybe Ronnie Coleman would have
gotten eight Mr. Olympia, nine Mr.
Olympias if he went deeper on his
squats. It's like you can point at the
one in a billion person who's successful
despite a a a bad behavior and say look
that but you can't correlate the bad
behavior with a a positive outcome. Nor
can you attribute a positive outcome to
a bad behavior when okay we've got the
survivorship bias and we got Michael
Phelps smoke weed got eight gold medals.
It's like right and there's 3
billion999,999,999
guys who didn't get gold medals. And of
those, a billion of them smoke weed.
That that despite being having this one
handicap, he's still the greatest of all
time. But that doesn't mean the handicap
made him better.
The dude had to eat 12,000 calories
worth of pasta a day. He did it by
giving himself the munchies with weed.
So there's a there's more factors
involved. This is something that
scientists don't seem to understand is
real life. Because when someone goes
into academia, the way that they get a
PhD is they know that if they left that
university, they wouldn't be able to
survive in the business world. So, they
have to stay in school and just go back
like, "Oh, I got my four-year degree,
but I don't I'm not ready to work. Mommy
and daddy are just going to pay for me
to get another degree." And then they
get a master's degree. Then they're
like, "Oh, I I don't really feel like
working. I'm just going to stay in
school and have mommy and daddy get me
another degree." And then they get a
PhD. And then, I mean, some of those
people work, but like not a lot. And
then eventually,
they have no choice. So, what do they
do? Well, they got a PhD, so now they
teach college.
That's and and now they're going to
teach other people how to get this
useless piece of paper that helps them
do nothing. And so that's basically how
academia is. It's a bunch of snobs that
have imposttor syndrome. They know
they're not actually worldly or
functional adults, but they are smart in
their field. So they constantly try to
make other people in their field look
stupid so that they can feel better
about themsel. And then that's all
academia is. And then they take this
grant money and they fund these studies
that are there to push their narrative.
Like they've got an idea of what outcome
they want. So they construct the method
section to get the outcome they're
looking for. They're not applying real
scientific theory, which is you have a
hypothesis, you try to prove the null
hypothesis. Try to prove yourself wrong
every [__] way possible. And if you
can't prove yourself wrong, you have no
choice but to be right. So I'm not
immune to this. What I do is I pay a
researcher to watch my videos and read
the stuff I do and try to find me prove
me wrong.
I actually pay someone to go through and
try to prove me wrong all the time. And
he's super brilliant with writing
prompts for AI. So he is a genius whose
special genius ability is
getting the most out of AI. And then he
con him and AI programs work on trying
to prove me wrong. And most of the time
it's like I'm 95% right and the 5% of
the time I'm wrong is some nuance like
well in this population in this country
they have this genetic mutation where
this might not happen. It's like but
they're not the people watching the
video so [__] them you know it doesn't
really matter. So like there's there's
like a coward's way out. One of the
coward ways out is to say, "Well, maybe
Masteron isn't an AI and maybe Primo is
an AI in some people, but in some people
it's reversed." It's like, but what is
some people? The way that they worded it
makes it sound like it's a 50/50 thing.
It ain't a 50/50 thing. It's like a 9010
thing or a 955 thing. We don't have to
address outliers. We don't need that
level of nuance. that once you put a
blanket statement down like everybody's
different and you might have a weird
response. Some people take um benzo and
get anxiety, that doesn't mean that we
shouldn't label like may cause anxiety
on every anti-anxiety med. I mean,
there's a certain shot that should have
said may cause actual death, but you
know,
that's neither here nor there. But we
don't have to say like that's like
saying on a painkiller may cause
increased pain. Well, then no one's
going to buy it and it's not even
relevant. It's not even a large
percentage of the population. So, you
got like a tiny fraction of people that
lose their hair for Masteron because
they're adding Masteron. They're not
replacing test with Masteron. They're
adding Masteron to a super overloaded
test cycle and they're doing the test
wrong. They're using a lot of tests
twice a week or three times a week. So,
their SHBG is high and it's holding a
ton of DHT. Then they add mass to it.
Mass to the cycle. The mass binds to the
DH to the SHG, bumps the DHT off. All
the DHT goes to their hair because
they're taking finasteride, which blocks
the prostate converting test to DHT, but
it doesn't block the hair from
converting test to DHT. And then they
start losing their hair. And then they
always say the same thing. It's like,
"Oh, when I'm taking a shower, there's a
handful of hair in my hand. It's filling
my trash can." It's always word for word
that exact story cuz they're lying. They
basically saw this myth, this urban
legend online. So, they dramatize it cuz
they're [__] The When the [__] else
do you touch your hair? You only touch
your hair in the shower. So, obviously,
if you're going to have any
hair in your hands, it's in the shower.
And you didn't start looking at your
hand counting the hairs until you took
the mastra. So you're having a
hypocchondriacal perception of a
response.
>> Yeah.
>> And that's all it is. You've got a
little bit of hair shedding.
>> You got a you've got a hypochondriacal
response where you're now hyperfocused
on the hair in your hands when you're
taking a shower because you heard this
story on the internet and you're only
looking because you're on Mastron. And
that would only happen if you're using
too much test and you're taking
infrequently. But everyone uses too much
test and everyone takes it infrequently.